Guide to the UTU Records
UTU Records
- Railroad Bibliography (Box 52, Folder 58)
- Railroad Ind. Rel. Project- Guidelines for Union (Box 52, Folder 59)
- Railroad Material- Misc. (Box 52, Folder 60)
- UTU Songbook (Box 52, Folder 61)
- Structure of C-B in Railroad Industry (Box 52, Folder 62)
- Thesis- Tentative Outline, The Unification of Operating Railroad Brotherhoods (Box 52, Folder 63)
- UTU Academic Brochure (Box 52, Folder 64)
- UTU- Bibliography (I. Blank) (Box 52, Folder 65)
- UTU- Canadian Autonomy (Box 52, Folder 66)
- UTU- Merser Hypotheses (Box 52, Folder 67)
- UTU- Public Relations Brochure (Box 52, Folder 68)
- UTU- Syracuse, Kenefeck and Wykle (Box 52, Folder 69)
- UTU- Misc. File (Box 52, Folder 70)
- Railroad Ind. Rel. Proj. Letterhead (Box 52, Folder 71)
- The Settlement f The American Railway Union Strike Against the Great Northern Railway in 1894, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 72)
- "The Railroad Brotherhoods and Railway Labor Act" (Box 52, Folder 73)
- Railroad Ind. Rel. Project- Guidelines For Mgmt. (Box 52, Folder 74)
- Joint Railway Labor History Project (Box 52, Folder 75)
- "Some Observations on the Problems of the Relationships Between Union and Management" (Box 52, Folder 76)
- "Revival of the Railroads- Whose Responsibility?" (Box 52, Folder 77)
- Vol. 4- 1972 (Box 52, Folder 78)
- Railroad Labor and Government Transportation Policy, 1962-1972 (Box 52, Folder 79)
- The Fireman-Off Controversy (Box 52, Folder 80)
- Railroad Labor Exhibits (Box 52, Folder 81)
- The Unification of Operating Brotherhoods (Box 52, Folder 82)
- High Speed Rail Assiv- (Box 53, Folder 1)
- High Speed Rail (Box 53, Folder 2)
- High Speed Rail (Box 53, Folder 3)
- "Fifth Annual Chairpersons Conference" (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Ohio Communications (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Texas Communications (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Nebraska Communications (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Arizona Communications (Box 53, Folder 8)
- Michigan Communications (Box 53, Folder 9)
- Washington, D.C. Communications (Box 53, Folder 10)
- Tennessee Communications (Box 53, Folder 11)
- "Retiree News" Vol. 15 (Box 53, Folder 12)
- UTU Agreements (Box 53, Folder 13)
- Texas A+M (Box 53, Folder 14)
- New York Central RR Statistics (Box 53, Folder 15)
- What the Loss of RR Jobs Means (Box 53, Folder 16)
- Southwestern Community College (Box 53, Folder 17)
- Hayden (Box 53, Folder 18)
- ICC Investigation P-C 3/72, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 19)
- Erie- Lackawanna (Box 53, Folder 20)
- Award Circular No. (11-90)-(15-90) (Box 53, Folder 21)
- Norfolk- Southern- DWC (Box 53, Folder 22)
- Advertisement (Box 53, Folder 23)
- United Transportation Union: One Direction Forward, One Future Solid, Choose UTU (Box 53, Folder 24)
- BETA Copies of Organizing Tape (Box 53, Folder 25)
- Proceedings of the Unification and Constitutional Convention Days 1-10 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Proceedings of the Unification and Constitutional Convention Days 11-20 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Proceedings of the Unification and Constitutional Convention Days 21-30 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  Missing 22, 23
- Proceedings of the Unification and Constitutional Convention Days 31-40 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  Missing 35-38
- Proceedings of the Unification and Constitutional Convention Days 41-50 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  Missing 44
- Proceedings of the Unification and Constitutional Convention Days 51-54 (Box 54, Folder 6)
- 1985 Directory- International Headquarters and Locals (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Am. Soybean Assoc. (Box 54, Folder 8)
- Misc. (Box 54, Folder 9)
- "Report of the Committee on Constitution- First Convention, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 10)
- "Report of the Committee on Constitution- First Convention, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 11)
- "Report of the Committee on Constitution- Second Convention, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 12)
- 1969 report- General Secretary and Treasurer (Box 54, Folder 13)
- 1970 Report- General Secretary and Treasurer (Box 54, Folder 14)
- 1971 Report- General Secretary and Treasurer (Box 54, Folder 15)
- 1971 Report- General Secretary and Treasurer (Box 54, Folder 16)
- 1972 Report- General Secretary and Treasurer (Box 54, Folder 17)
- 1977 Report- General Secretary and Treasurer (Box 54, Folder 18)
- 1979 Report- General Secretary and Treasurer (Box 54, Folder 19)
- 1971 Report of the Board of Directors (Box 54, Folder 20)
- Report of the Committee on International Officers' Reports- First Convention, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 21)
- Report of the Committee on International Officers' Reports- First Convention, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 22)
- 1971 (Box 54, Folder 23)
- United Transportation Union Insurance Association (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Task Force on Rail Transportation (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Terminal Task Force, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- A Prospectus for Change in the Freight Railroad Industry (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Conrail at the Crossroads: The Future of Rail Service in the Northeast, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Labor Report to Congress, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Federal Funding of Conrail: Rail Service Objectives and Economic Realities, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 7)
- "Railroad Companies and the Operating Crafts: The Work Rules Controversy Since 1945, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 8)
- "Evaluation of the National Council on Alcoholism Labor/Management Task Force Project on Employee Alcoholism" (Box 55, Folder 9)
- TRW Seminar- St. Louis (Box 55, Folder 10)
- Speech Material (Box 55, Folder 11)
- Speech Material (Box 55, Folder 12)
- Handling Hazardous Materials (Box 55, Folder 13)
- Norfolk Southern (Box 55, Folder 14)
- Operation Red Block (Box 55, Folder 15)
- Succession of Larger Contracts- 1989 (Box 55, Folder 16)
- Forced Mergers, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 17)
- "Terminal Performance Measurement System", 1979 (Box 55, Folder 18)
- "Background" Vol. 21, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 19)
- Hunan Affair (Box 55, Folder 20)
- "Labor-Management Committees: Factors Affecting the Degree of Cooperative Problem Solving Behavior" (Box 55, Folder 21)
- Southern Pacific Transportation Co. (Box 55, Folder 22)
- ORTA (Box 55, Folder 23)
- Conrail (Box 55, Folder 24)
- Milw. (Box 55, Folder 25)
- Rail Reorganization Act- 1973 (Box 55, Folder 26)
- Chicago Central Pacific (Box 55, Folder 27)
- 1971 (Box 56, Folder 1)
- 1972 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- 1973 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- 1974 (Box 56, Folder 4)
- 1975 (Box 56, Folder 5)
- 1976 (Box 56, Folder 6)
- Exhibits IA-IF, 2A-2Z (Box 56, Folder 7)
- Exhibits 3A-3H (Box 56, Folder 8)
- State of Kansas - Correspondence., 1983 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  corresponding cassettes went to 5139 AV
- "Final Report- Seminar on Interchange of Empty Cars", 1978 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Consolidation and Merges (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Houston Terminal Project, 1981 (Box 57, Folder 3)
- System Steering Committee (Box 57, Folder 4)
- "Emergency Board 195- Transcript of Presentations by National Railway Labor Conference and UTU" (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Index- Exhibit 14 (Box 57, Folder 6)
- The Effects of Technological Change on Working Knowledge in Rail Switching (Box 57, Folder 7)
- Sequence of Events- Committee of Four- ORC-B-BRT-BLF+E-SUNA (Box 57, Folder 8)
- Chicago- Central- Pacific (Box 57, Folder 9)
- Blue Ribbon Panel (Box 57, Folder 10)
- 1988 Survey Analysis (Box 57, Folder 11)
- Southern Missouri Pacific and Milwaukee Railroads (Box 57, Folder 12)
- "Your Future Demands Decisions Based on Facts." (Box 57, Folder 13)
- B-N Wage Proposal- 7/1/88, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 14)
- Rue G- Redblock Operation, Drug and Alcohol, EAP (Box 57, Folder 15)
- Pro-UTU Pamphlets, Flyers (Box 57, Folder 16)
- Car Utilization Study (Box 57, Folder 17)
- Employee Requests (Box 57, Folder 18)
- ACT (Box 57, Folder 19)
- Coupling (Box 57, Folder 20)
- EAP Activity Report, 1972-1985 (Box 57, Folder 21)
- EAP Activity Report, 1972-1986 (Box 57, Folder 22)
- Field Manual Appendix (Box 57, Folder 23)
- "Annual Statement of the United Transportation Union Insurance Association", 1980 (Box 58, Folder 1)
- UTU Promotional Pieces, Alcohol and Drugs, Policies (Box 58, Folder 2)
- Interview with Fred A. Hardin, 1987 (Box 58, Folder 3)
- An Update on a Feasibility Study on the Council Bluffs to Brunswick Short-line Railroad (Box 58, Folder 4)
- Transportation Maps (Box 58, Folder 5)
- "Regional Meeting" (Box 58, Folder 6)
- "The Railroader's Handbook" (Box 58, Folder 7)
- Member's Time Book (Box 58, Folder 8)
- GCA Committees by Local, Title and Amount of Assessment by Local (Box 58, Folder 9)
- Directory- International Headquarters and Locals, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 10)
- 1985 (Box 58, Folder 11)
- Meeting- May 25- Historical (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Initial Claim and Grievance Processing (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Correspondence on Artifacts for Railroad History Museum, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 3)
- Fourth Annual Chairpersons Conference, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- UTU Correspondence. (Box 59, Folder 5)
- New England Rail Restructuring Analysis, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 6)
- New England Rail Restructuring Analysis, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 7)
- "Background" Vol. 10, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 8)
- Houston Terminal Project, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Labor Research Coordinators' Files (Box 59, Folder 10)
- In the United States District Court for the Eastern District of Missouri (Box 59, Folder 11)
- Pennsylvania Railroad Co. an New York Central Railroad Co. Merger (Box 59, Folder 12)
- New England Rail Restructuring Study (Box 59, Folder 13)
- Analysis of Selected Coordination Opportunities of the New England Railroads (Box 59, Folder 14)
- Improving Railroad Productivity (Box 59, Folder 15)
- South Dakota Rail Plan, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 16)
- South Dakota Railplan, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 17)
- Amendment to Rail Plan South Dakota (Box 59, Folder 18)
- Terminal Performance Measurement Systems (Box 59, Folder 19)
- UTU- Report and Claim Procedures Manual (Box 59, Folder 20)
- Regional Rail Reorganization Act, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 21)
- Regional Rail Reorganization Act, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 22)
- An Index Digest of Procedural Awards of Public Law Boards, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 23)
- General Secretary and Treasurer's Annual Report, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 24)
- Field Manual Appendix (Box 59, Folder 25)
- Field Manual Appendix- Vol. 3 (Box 59, Folder 26)
- Counselor Training (Box 65, Folder 1)
- Troubled Track (Box 65, Folder 2)
- RR Economics (Box 65, Folder 3)
- Rail Consolidations (Box 65, Folder 4)
- Praise of Trains (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Motor Carrier vs. Rail Costs (Box 65, Folder 6)
- Motor Carrier vs. Rail Costs (Box 65, Folder 7)
- "The Truth About American Ground Transport" (Box 65, Folder 8)
- Safety (Box 65, Folder 9)
- Northeast Rail line Corp. (Box 65, Folder 10)
- SEPTA (Box 65, Folder 11)
- Truth About Ground Transport (Box 65, Folder 12)
- Supreme Court (Box 65, Folder 13)
- Random Testing Implement (Box 65, Folder 14)
- Labor Mgmt. Committee (Box 65, Folder 15)
- In the United States Court of Appeals for the Ninth Circuit (Box 65, Folder 16)
- In the United States Court of Appeals for the Ninth Circuit (Box 65, Folder 17)
- From RLEA for Publication (Box 65, Folder 18)
- In the United States Court of Appeals for the Ninth Circuit (Box 65, Folder 19)
- In the Supreme Court of the United States Oct. Term, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 20)
- Status- Highways, Bridges- 1989 (Box 65, Folder 21)
- Operation Red Block (Box 66, Folder 1)
- Draft Minutes Oct. 24, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- "Along the Overland Route", 1991 (Box 66, Folder 3)
- RLEA- Alcohol (Box 66, Folder 4)
- Drugs (Box 66, Folder 5)
- DOT and the Unions (Box 66, Folder 6)
- Collins (Box 66, Folder 7)
- Rail Reorganization Act, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 8)
- Railroad Collectibles, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 9)
- American Men- Super standard and Substandard Tables and extension of Table to Age 0 (Box 66, Folder 10)
- Conrail '81 Memos, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 11)
- Conrail- Crisis Special Edition (Box 66, Folder 12)
- Conrail, Mar. '81, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 13)
- Conrail, Wage-deferral '81, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 14)
- Special Court (Box 66, Folder 15)
- "Evaluation of the U.S. Railway Association's Preliminary System Plan" (Box 66, Folder 16)
- Conrail- Consolidation Rail Corporation (Box 66, Folder 17)
- News Clippings (Box 66, Folder 18)
- Conrail (Box 66, Folder 19)
- Conrail (Box 66, Folder 20)
- Conrail (Box 66, Folder 21)
- Northern Crisis '73, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 22)
- 1973 (Box 66, Folder 23)
- RLEA-Conrail Task Force (Box 67, Folder 1)
- UTU-Conrail Agreements (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Conrail '81-'82 (1 out of 3) (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Conrail '81-'82 (2 out of 3) (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Conrail '81-'82 (3 out of 3) (Box 67, Folder 5)
- Conrail (Box 67, Folder 6)
- Conrail '81 Clippings and Photos (Box 67, Folder 7)
- UTU NewsConRail (Box 67, Folder 8)
- Morgan Stanley Proposal (Box 67, Folder 9)
- (Box 67, Folder 10)
- "Minutes of Annual Meeting of General Chairmen's' Assn'. (Box 68, Folder 1)
- "Manual of Information and Instructions" (Box 68, Folder 2)
- Report- Joint Relations Committee Cleveland Convention, 1935 (Box 68, Folder 3)
- G.W. Hunt (Box 68, Folder 4)
- National Railroad Adjustment Board- First Edition (Box 68, Folder 5)
- Procedure Manual (Box 68, Folder 6)
- Negotiating Manual (Box 68, Folder 7)
- (Box 68, Folder 8)
- Employee Assistance Programs (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Labor Management Project News (Box 69, Folder 2)
- EAP Activity Reports (Box 69, Folder 3)
- Copy of Group Policy Contract (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Group Insurance Plan as amended effective March 1, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 5)
- Group Hospital Surgical and Medical Insurance Plan (Box 69, Folder 6)
- SUMA Locals 12/68 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- CSX Oversight Meeting (Box 69, Folder 8)
- Travelers (Box 69, Folder 9)
- Drugs and Alcohol Control (Box 69, Folder 10)
- Teamsters "No Raid" Agreement July 31, 1972 (Box 69, Folder 11)
- Alcoholism (Box 69, Folder 12)
- Summary, Phase I Rail Alcoholism Programs (Box 69, Folder 13)
- Task Force Speeches (Box 69, Folder 14)
- Training (Box 69, Folder 15)
- Operation Red Block (Box 69, Folder 16)
- DOT and the Unions (Box 69, Folder 17)
- Woods Hole (Box 69, Folder 18)
- BLE-UTU Unification (Box 69, Folder 19)
- (Box 69, Folder 20)
- St. Louis L-M Task Force (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Conrail Labor-Management Task Force (Box 70, Folder 2)
- Labor Management Task Force St. Louis (Box 70, Folder 3)
- Buffalo, New York Labor Management Task Force (Box 70, Folder 4)
- Conrail Labor Management Task Force (Box 70, Folder 5)
- (Box 70, Folder 6)
- UTU Communications (Box 71, Folder 1)
- "Decade of Decision" (Box 71, Folder 2)
- CSX July '87 (Box 71, Folder 3)
- Highways for Survival (Box 71, Folder 4)
- Milwaukee (Box 71, Folder 5)
- Terminal Task Force 1971 (Box 71, Folder 6)
- Protection (Box 71, Folder 7)
- Rochester and Southern RR (Box 71, Folder 8)
- Role of Labor (Box 71, Folder 9)
- Association of American Railroads (Box 71, Folder 10)
- Technical Report Data (Box 71, Folder 11)
- Quality Action Council Meeting- Tampa (Box 71, Folder 12)
- Genesee and Wyoming (Box 72, Folder 1)
- Road Railers (Box 72, Folder 2)
- CSX L-M (Box 72, Folder 3)
- Amtrak (Box 72, Folder 4)
- B-N Rule G Study (Box 72, Folder 5)
- Task Force on Rail Transportation (Box 72, Folder 6)
- Employee Protection (Box 72, Folder 7)
- UTU Organizer's Handbook (Box 72, Folder 8)
- A Study of the Economics of Short Trains (Box 72, Folder 9)
- Testing Agreements (Box 72, Folder 10)
- 1992-1993 Directory (Box 72, Folder 11)
- New England Labor Management Task Force (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Buffalo, New York Labor Management Task Force (Box 73, Folder 2)
- New England Task Force (Box 73, Folder 3)
- Buffalo Task Forces (Box 73, Folder 4)
- Proposed Unification Agreement (Box 74, Folder 1)
- Hardin on Work Rules (Box 74, Folder 2)
- ICG Slingshot (Box 74, Folder 3)
- Strike Policy '85, 1985 (Box 74, Folder 4)
- Sprints (Milw.) (Box 74, Folder 5)
- Intermodal Feasibility Study (Box 74, Folder 6)
- U-P--L-M (Box 74, Folder 7)
- Rail Opportunities (Box 74, Folder 8)
- QWL- Cleveland (Box 74, Folder 9)
- Public Ownership- Rail Right of Way (Box 74, Folder 10)
- RR Accounting Practice- Regulation Transportation (Box 74, Folder 11)
- Union Concessions (Box 74, Folder 12)
- Piggyback (Box 74, Folder 13)
- Ann Arbor (Box 74, Folder 14)
- Featherbedding on Railroads- Proposed Nat'l Ry Act-1976 (Box 74, Folder 15)
- Staggers Act- 1980 (Box 74, Folder 16)
- 1991 Report (1 of 3) (Box 74, Folder 17)
- 1991 Report (2 of 3) (Box 74, Folder 18)
- 1991 Report (3 of 3) (Box 74, Folder 19)
- Labor Reports and News (Box 74, Folder 20)
- Voting Details (Box 74, Folder 21)
- Agreements and Disputes (Box 74, Folder 22)
- Award Circular (Box 74, Folder 23)
- Labor Acts and Laws (Box 74, Folder 24)
- Index (Box 74, Folder 25)
- Informative Booklets (Box 74, Folder 26)
- "Research on the Treatment of Narcotic Addiction" (Box 75, Folder 1)
- Rail-Based Transportation of Export-Destined Wheat (Box 75, Folder 2)
- Rail-Based Transportation of Export-Destined Wheat (Box 75, Folder 3)
- C+O B+O Alcohol Programs (Box 75, Folder 4)
- Alcoholism Programs (Box 75, Folder 5)
- Metro North (Box 75, Folder 6)
- New Clippings (Box 75, Folder 7)
- U.S. Public Transportation Program: Toward a Balanced System (Box 75, Folder 8)
- UTU: Report and Claim, Procedures, Governing (Box 75, Folder 9)
- Report of the Committee on Constitution-1979 (1 of 2) (Box 75, Folder 10)
- Report of the Committee on Constitution-1979 (2 of 2) (Box 75, Folder 11)
- Class I- Line-Haul Railroads (Box 75, Folder 12)
- Interstate Commerce Commission- Occupational Classification Codes (Box 75, Folder 13)
- Ohio High Speed Rail Passenger Plan (Phase 1) (Box 75, Folder 14)
- Reports and Current Developments (Box 75, Folder 15)
- Correspondence (Box 75, Folder 16)
- Wage-Rules Movement (Box 75, Folder 17)
- "Nickel Rate Road" (Box 75, Folder 18)
- UTU Constitution (Box 75, Folder 19)
- "Rules of the Transportation Department" (Box 75, Folder 20)
- "The Law of Labor Relations" (Box 75, Folder 21)
- Free Collective Bargaining vs. Compulsory Arbitration (Box 75, Folder 22)
- The Railway Labor Act (Box 75, Folder 23)
- British Colombia Ry (Box 76, Folder 1)
- MKT (Box 76, Folder 2)
- Birmingham Southern (Box 76, Folder 3)
- B-N (Box 76, Folder 4)
- Logic-Work Rules (Box 76, Folder 5)
- Colorado and Wyoming (Box 76, Folder 6)
- Boston and Maine (Box 76, Folder 7)
- Mo-Pac Alcoholism (Box 76, Folder 8)
- Alcoholism- Illinois Central (Box 76, Folder 9)
- Illinois Terminal (Box 76, Folder 10)
- Indiana Harbor Beet (Box 76, Folder 11)
- KCS (Box 76, Folder 12)
- Union Record Acquisitions (Box 76, Folder 13)
- KCS (Box 76, Folder 14)
- Long Island RR (Box 76, Folder 15)
- L+N (Box 76, Folder 16)
- Maine Central (Box 76, Folder 17)
- Monongahela Connecting RR (Box 76, Folder 18)
- DRGW (Box 76, Folder 19)
- DT+I (Box 76, Folder 20)
- Green Bay and Western (Box 76, Folder 21)
- Houston Beet and Terminal (Box 76, Folder 22)
- Indiana Harbor Belt (Box 76, Folder 23)
- Indianapolis Union RY (Box 76, Folder 24)
- Frisco (Box 76, Folder 25)
- Grand Trunk (Box 76, Folder 26)
- Vermont (Box 76, Folder 27)
- Delray Connecting (Box 76, Folder 28)
- C-N-W (Box 76, Folder 29)
- Erie- Lackawanna (Box 76, Folder 30)
- Chicago Northwestern (Box 76, Folder 31)
- Canadian Pacific (Box 76, Folder 32)
- Bangor and Aroostook (Box 76, Folder 33)
- Bessemer + Lake Erie (Box 76, Folder 34)
- Alaska (Box 76, Folder 35)
- Adirondack Transit (Box 76, Folder 36)
- Correspondence (Box 76, Folder 37)
- News Clippings (Box 76, Folder 38)
- "The Pros and Cons of Compulsory Arbitration" (Box 76, Folder 39)
- D.W.C. Speeches (Box 76, Folder 40)
- "The Lighted Flame" (Box 76, Folder 41)
- "The Empire That Missouri Pacific Serves" (Box 76, Folder 42)
- BLE-UTU Canada (Box 76, Folder 43)
- The OSAP Prevention Pipeline (Box 76, Folder 44)
- The OSAP Prevention Pipeline (Box 76, Folder 45)
- (Box 76, Folder 46)
- Rule 6- Bypass Agreement (Box 77, Folder 1)
- UTU Position on Breathalyzer (Box 77, Folder 2)
- SP-Breathalyzer (Box 77, Folder 3)
- SP (Certification Rule G.) (Box 77, Folder 4)
- Misc. Presentations (Box 77, Folder 5)
- Employee Assistance Annual Program Evaluation- 1991 (Box 77, Folder 6)
- RR Drug Abuse and Prevention Act (Box 77, Folder 7)
- Juanita: Yesterday and Today (Box 77, Folder 8)
- Training in Communication Skills (Box 77, Folder 9)
- Labor/Management Project (Box 77, Folder 10)
- Bus Files in Storage (Box 77, Folder 11)
- New Business Trains (Box 77, Folder 12)
- G and Da Bose (Box 77, Folder 13)
- T. Unions- Democracy (Box 77, Folder 14)
- Strike (Box 77, Folder 15)
- Amtrak Labor-Management (Box 77, Folder 16)
- Albany, NY- Cornell (Box 77, Folder 17)
- USAT Bulletin (Box 77, Folder 18)
- News Clippings (Box 77, Folder 19)
- Agreements (Box 77, Folder 20)
- Manual of Working Conditions Applicable to International Employees of the United Transportation Union (Box 77, Folder 21)
- UTU- BLE Canadian Council (Box 77, Folder 22)
- The Railway Labor Executives' Association Employee Assistance Program Workshop (Box 77, Folder 23)
- Alcohol- AFL- CIO (Box 77, Folder 24)
- National Transportation Safety Board (Box 77, Folder 25)
- UTU Strike (Box 77, Folder 26)
- Grady Cothen FRA (Box 77, Folder 27)
- "Providing for Unemployed Workers in the Transition" (Box 77, Folder 28)
- (Box 77, Folder 29)
- "Background"- Vol. 15 (Box 78, Folder 1)
- Buffalo Terminal Project Progress Reports (Box 78, Folder 2)
- Buffalo Terminal Project Progress Reports (Box 78, Folder 3)
- Correspondence (Box 78, Folder 4)
- Disputes and Agreements (Box 78, Folder 5)
- Alcohol, Drug Abuse, and Mental Health Administration- Dept. of Health and Human Services (Box 78, Folder 6)
- Railroad Retirement Board Annual Report- 1990 (Box 78, Folder 7)
- In the Supreme Court of the United States (Box 78, Folder 8)
- In the Supreme Court of the United States (Box 78, Folder 9)
- In the Supreme Court of the United States (Box 78, Folder 10)
- John F. Collins (Box 78, Folder 11)
- In the Supreme Court of the United States (Box 78, Folder 12)
- In the Supreme Court of the United States (Box 78, Folder 13)
- In the Supreme Court of the United States (Box 78, Folder 14)
- Conrail in Perspective- 1983 (Box 78, Folder 15)
- Qualifications for Locomotive Engineers (Box 78, Folder 16)
- New England Drug Use Survey (Box 78, Folder 17)
- Short Line Agreement between Kyle Railroad Co. and UTU (Box 78, Folder 18)
- Burlington Northern Employee Assistance Program (Box 78, Folder 19)
- Memorandum of Settlement (Box 78, Folder 20)
- Southern Pacific and Drug Testing (Box 78, Folder 21)
- Statement of John Risch (Box 78, Folder 22)
- News (Box 78, Folder 23)
- '91 Convention (Box 78, Folder 24)
- '87 Convention (Box 78, Folder 25)
- Museum (Box 78, Folder 26)
- Award Circulars (Box 78, Folder 27)
- Hardin Statement (Box 78, Folder 28)
- SP Breathalyzer (Box 78, Folder 29)
- Employment Records (Box 78, Folder 30)
- "People on the Move" (Box 78, Folder 31)
- (Box 78, Folder 32)
- Field Manual (Box 79, Folder 1)
- Federal Control of Railroads (Box 79, Folder 2)
- News and Updates (Box 79, Folder 3)
- Correspondence (Box 79, Folder 4)
- Murphy Case (Box 79, Folder 5)
- American Short Line Railway Guide (Box 79, Folder 6)
- United Transportation Union Research and Statistical Dept. Telephone Directory (Box 79, Folder 7)
- ART (Box 79, Folder 8)
- 1991 Directory (Box 79, Folder 9)
- Houston Labor Management Task Force (Box 79, Folder 10)
- Railroads of Alabama (Box 79, Folder 11)
- Emergency Board (Box 79, Folder 12)
- Article XX (Box 79, Folder 13)
- Mike Walsh Letter (Box 79, Folder 14)
- DOT Skinner (Box 79, Folder 15)
- AFL-CIO. Gateway Western (Box 79, Folder 16)
- Taskforce on Rail Transportation (Box 79, Folder 17)
- Rail Crisis (Box 79, Folder 18)
- UTU- Rail Abandonments (Box 79, Folder 19)
- FRA- Joe Walsh (Box 79, Folder 20)
- Houston Task Force (Box 79, Folder 21)
- Congressional Report (Box 79, Folder 22)
- DMIR (Box 79, Folder 23)
- Complaints (Box 79, Folder 24)
- A Curriculum of Study for Professional Practitioners (Box 79, Folder 25)